Tower says: Balloon# B1 (1) registered to weather tower.
Tower says: Balloon# B2 (2) registered to weather tower.
Tower says: JetPlane# J1 (3) registered to weather tower.
Tower says: Helicopter# H1 (4) registered to weather tower.
Tower says: Helicopter# H2 (5) registered to weather tower.
Tower says: Helicopter# H3 (6) registered to weather tower.
Tower says: Balloon# B3 (7) registered to weather tower.
Tower says: JetPlane# J2 (8) registered to weather tower.
Tower says: Helicopter# H4 (9) registered to weather tower.
Balloon# B1 (1): With this kind of heat we don't even need a torch to keep afloat.
Balloon# B2 (2): What'd happen if I threw a snowball from up here?
JetPlane# J1 (3): *pants heavily whilst sweating profusely*
Helicopter# H1 (4): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
Helicopter# H2 (5): Who thought it was a good idea to not put doors on this thing!?
Helicopter# H3 (6): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
Balloon# B3 (7): With this kind of heat we don't even need a torch to keep afloat.
JetPlane# J2 (8): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
Helicopter# H4 (9): Look, it's like we're making a tiny tornado above us
Balloon# B1 (1): What'd happen if I threw a snowball from up here?
Balloon# B2 (2): What'd happen if I threw a snowball from up here?
JetPlane# J1 (3): *pants heavily whilst sweating profusely*
Helicopter# H1 (4): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
Helicopter#H1(4): landing.
Tower says: Helicopter#H1(4) unregistered from weather tower.
Helicopter# H2 (5): Who thought it was a good idea to not put doors on this thing!?
Helicopter# H3 (6): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
Balloon# B3 (7): What'd happen if I threw a snowball from up here?
Balloon#B3(7): landing.
Tower says: Balloon#B3(7) unregistered from weather tower.
JetPlane# J2 (8): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
Helicopter# H4 (9): Who thought it was a good idea to not put doors on this thing!?
Balloon# B1 (1): What'd happen if I threw a snowball from up here?
Balloon#B1(1): landing.
Tower says: Balloon#B1(1) unregistered from weather tower.
Balloon# B2 (2): With this kind of heat we don't even need a torch to keep afloat.
JetPlane# J1 (3): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
Helicopter# H2 (5): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
Helicopter# H3 (6): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
JetPlane# J2 (8): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
Helicopter# H4 (9): Who thought it was a good idea to not put doors on this thing!?
Balloon# B2 (2): Let's hope THIS 'water balloon' doesn't burst.
Balloon#B2(2): landing.
Tower says: Balloon#B2(2) unregistered from weather tower.
JetPlane# J1 (3): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
Helicopter# H2 (5): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
Helicopter#H2(5): landing.
Tower says: Helicopter#H2(5) unregistered from weather tower.
Helicopter# H3 (6): Who thought it was a good idea to not put doors on this thing!?
JetPlane# J2 (8): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
Helicopter# H4 (9): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
JetPlane# J1 (3): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
Helicopter# H3 (6): Who thought it was a good idea to not put doors on this thing!?
JetPlane# J2 (8): I can't see anything -_-
Helicopter# H4 (9): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
Helicopter#H4(9): landing.
Tower says: Helicopter#H4(9) unregistered from weather tower.
JetPlane# J1 (3): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
JetPlane#J1(3): landing.
Tower says: JetPlane#J1(3) unregistered from weather tower.
Helicopter# H3 (6): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
JetPlane# J2 (8): You think i can make a snow angel in a building? ba-dum-tss...
Helicopter# H3 (6): Sure wish the fan on this thing was on the inside...
JetPlane# J2 (8): You think i can make a snow angel in a building? ba-dum-tss...
Helicopter# H3 (6): I do love me some shaved ice
JetPlane# J2 (8): You think i can make a snow angel in a building? ba-dum-tss...
Helicopter# H3 (6): I do love me some shaved ice
Helicopter#H3(6): landing.
Tower says: Helicopter#H3(6) unregistered from weather tower.
JetPlane# J2 (8): *pants heavily whilst sweating profusely*
JetPlane# J2 (8): *pants heavily whilst sweating profusely*
JetPlane# J2 (8): *pants heavily whilst sweating profusely*
JetPlane# J2 (8): *pants heavily whilst sweating profusely*
JetPlane# J2 (8): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
JetPlane# J2 (8): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
JetPlane# J2 (8): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
JetPlane# J2 (8): We should start a company that sells sprinklers...
JetPlane#J2(8): landing.
Tower says: JetPlane#J2(8) unregistered from weather tower.
